Hello friends, welcome to Kaise Commando. So
friends, if you are new to this channel, then please
subscribe to the channel and also
press the bell icon and
click on it so that you keep
getting regular updates. So friends, today is
18th April, the
result of the insurance quarter has come,
so let us check its result.
Before that, you guys can see here
how much dividend the company has given.
You can see here that the
company has given a dividend of ₹550 and
its face value is Rs.
Now if you look at the revenue form operation, then the
company has a lot of income, if we
go directly to its net income, then the
total income of the company in this quarter is 525,
you can see here that it is
52558 lakhs, so I will take a round figure for
you to understand, so
in this quarter it was 525, in the previous quarter it was
436 and if we talk about 1 year ago, then 1 year
ago it was 463, you can see, so
we have seen a slight decline.
Now after the income, we have come to the matter of expenditure,
so here also you can see, there is a
lot of expenditure of this, so we will
directly look at its expenditure, so
in this quarter the total expenditure of the company is 397, if we
talk about the previous, the
profit before tax in which order is 57, if we
look at it in the previous quarter, then it was 46
and after one year ago, then one year ago it was
41, so here on a quarter on quarter
basis and air on air basis the
profit of the company has grown tremendously, now
all the tax etc. has been adjusted, so you
can see your tax, in this quarter it was
43, in the previous quarter it was 35
and if we talk about one year ago, then one year
ago it was 31, so here also you can see that
we are getting good growth in profit,
friends, I am not talking about many of its points,
I am
telling you the amplifier, by the way, when you will
see the result, then every point has to be
looked at carefully, but I will
tell you the rough figures, as
you  People can see here the company's result
and surplus
to see how boring it is, it is not showing here,
but it will definitely be boring, friends,
now we
can see here that the company has a loss of 7.137 in the previous quarter,
it makes a loss in the insurance sector,
so it becomes important to see this as well,
friends, it is not showing here,
now those who have a finance
background solve all this in a good way, a
little normality becomes appropriate for us,
and before this,
here you can see how big the
DIG is, so if we
talk about the overall result, friends, if you
see the current market price of the company, it is
running at 1136, today approximately
[music]
47% in 5 years and if we talk about the maximum, then the
maximum is 67%, that is, it has been
listed since 2017, till now it has
given only 67% of it, so we close the video here, we
hope that you all
liked this video, if you
liked it,
see you in the next video, till then,
thank you.